0on.info 2015-06-29

# Privacy Policy

### 

**Information Collection and Use**

Makeeasymoney-makingeasymoney.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Makeeasymoney-makingeasymoney.com collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
**  
**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Web Statistics**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user  
movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use for  
reporting and sponsorship purposes. IP addresses are not linked to personally  
identifiable information.

**Sharing**

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners, sponsors,  
and donors. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any  
individual person. We only share this information so that we can secure funding  
to continue providing this site free of charge.

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that [Organization]  
does not claim any responsibility for the privacy practices of such other sites.  
We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read  
the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally  
identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information  
collected by this Web site.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our  
home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how  
we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we  
decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that  
stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by e-mail. Users will have  
a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.  
We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the  
information was collected.
